Kyle Rassweiler

Chone: +1-613-724-9141
Email: jobs@kylerassweiler.ca

∆ Portfolio: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca
 ☐ Github: www.qithub.com/rassweiler

Summary

Engineering Specialist with experience in: software development, networking, programmable logic controllers, robotics, electronics, and machining.

Skills

Software Angular, Assembly(PIC), C++, CMake, Django, Git, HTML, JavaScript,

Mongoose, Node, PHP, Python, React, Redux

Virtualisation Docker, Qemu/KVM, XCP-NG

Systems Arch, Debian, FreeBSD/OpenBSD, Proxmox, Windows

Databases MongoDB, MySQL, Postgresql, SQLite

Hardware Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Zigbee

Projects

React Pagination

(Javascript, CSS, HTML, Node, React)

A Hatchways assesment for React front-end work. The project required the addition of a pagination system for a sample blog site.

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/hatchways-react-pagination

Random Quote Machine

(Javascript, CSS, HTML, Node, React, Bootstrap)

A FreeCodeCamp project that generates random tweetable quotes using React.

Website: https://codepen.io/kylerassweiler/pen/rNdJzYO

Krello

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node, React, Redux)

A simple Trello clone developed using react and redux with jest and enzyme for testing. Used Javascript, SCSS, and HTML to style the react components.

Website:

https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/posts/software/node/krello/

Demo: https://krello.kylerassweiler.com/ Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/krello

Kawasaki AS Parser

(Typescript, SCSS, HTML, Node, Electron)

A Kawasaki robot backup parser written in TypeScript for browser or Node. The library also includes TypeScript interfaces for use in new projects.

Website:

https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/posts/software/node/kawasaki-

parser/

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/kawasaki-as-parser

Certificates

Free Code Camp JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/kylerassweiler/

July 2022 javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

Free Code Camp

Responsive Web Design

June 2022

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/kylerassweiler/ responsive-web-design

Experience

Engineering Specialist

Robotics Technician

PLC programming, Robotic Vision (Robeye system), 3D Factory

Design, Robot programming, Project Management

2017 – Present

TEMA (Toyota)

PLC programming, Robot programming, SCADA programing.

2014 - 2017

FIO Automotive

Operational Technician

PLC programming, Robot programming.

2012 - 2014

Abbott Point Of Care

Education

Electro-Mechanical Engineering Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON. Technician

2010 - 2012

Computer Animation

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON.

2007 - 2010